eskhosting.com 2012-10-05

# Privacy policy

**Eskhosting Privacy Statement**

The present privacy policy was designed in an effort to protect our clients' and web site visitors` privacy and rights. Eskhosting is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its products and services.

**Collecting information. Privacy of your registration data**

Eskhosting and its agents and representatives collect personal information in a number of circumstances in the course of providing web hosting and domain name registration services to customers. Eskhosting may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. Personal information we collect may include:

  * Contact Information: Name, address, telephone number, email address and other contact information; 
  * Financial Information: Credit card numbers, bank name, billing address, transaction and purchase history with Eskhosting; 
  * Usage Information and History: Eskhosting usernames and passwords, IP address, support ticket history; 
  * Such other information we may collect with consent or as permitted or required by law.  
We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), the industry standard, for encrypting all personal information, including name, address and etc to ensure that the information is strongly protected against loss, alteration or misuse. Eskhosting keep all your information confidential. 

**Disclosure of your personal information**

Eskhosting discloses personal information only as necessary to meet legal, regulatory, audit, processing and security requirements, with your consent, or as permitted or required by law. Eskhosting will not disclose your personal information unless we believe that such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm with the rights or property of Eskhosting, Eskhosting customers or others, where Eskhosting has a good faith belief that the law requires any such disclosure.

Further to above said, personal information may be disclosed for internal audit, management, billing or administrative purposes.

In no event will Eskhosting disclose any personal information about its users to third parties without the customer's express written consent unless it is required by law procedures.

**Cookies**

Eskhosting understands that many of you are concerned about cookies. These are elements of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and are stored on your computer's hard drive. These files do not damage your system in any way. Cookies are used to identify what visitors look for on a web-site so that it can be more easily accessible in the future. We use cookies only for our Affiliate program purposes as it should operate in a correct and fair way. A cookie can't read data of your hard drive disk or another cookie files.

**Privacy Statement Changes**

This privacy statement may be revised from time to time. If we mean to use or disclose personal information for purposes that differ from those described in the present privacy policy, we will make reasonable efforts to notify affected individuals in advance, if necessary. If you are concerned about how your personal information is used, you should contact us as described above or check back at our website periodically to obtain a current copy of this statement. This privacy statement is effective as of August 1st, 2006.
